Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series VI. Communications and Marketing
  - Press Releases and Publications
    - Federal Club publications (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Building Equality, October 11, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Equality: A Winning Message, 1998 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Justice for All, 2004 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Equality from State to State, 2004 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - 2005 dinners, galas, fundraisers (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - A Time in History: 4th Annual HRC Leadership Summit, April 28-May 1, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Our Kitchen Table Issues (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Youth College Campaign Training, August 14-20, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - National Dinner letter head and envelopes, 2004-04 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - Corporate Equality Index, 2005-10 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Faith and Fairness Washington, DC town hall palmcard, 2005-11 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Buyers Guide, 2005-11 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, 2005-12 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Equality from State to State, 2005-12 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Corporate sponsor envelope, 2006-01 (Box 135, Folder 58)
    - Family Project "Best Interest of Child" palmcard, 2006-02 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - American Airlines business card, 2006-03 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Corporate Partnership brochure, 2006-03 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Oscar house party postcards, 2006-03 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Membership forms, 2006-03 (Box 135, Folder 57)
    - Vote No postcards with Equality Florida, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 95)
    - Vote No postcards, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 96)
    - George Takei/Coming Out Tour brochure, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 97)
    - Corporate Equality Index brochure, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 98)
    - Leadership Summit Save the Date, invitation, reply card, schedule, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 99)
    - Official Guide to Pride, 2006-04 (Box 133, Folder 100)
    - Religion and Faith "Changing the Conversation" palmcard, 2006-04 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Credit card bind-in, 2006-04 (Box 135, Folder 56)
    - Pride Join flyers, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 89)
    - Store catalogue, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 90)
    - Pride merchandise sheet, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 91)
    - Faith and Fairness Orlando palmcard, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 92)
    - Faith and Fairness Orlando town hall poster, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 93)
    - Family Project palmcard, 2006-05 (Box 133, Folder 94)
    - Coming Out Guide, 2006-06 (Box 133, Folder 87)
    - Out in Scripture, 2006-06 (Box 133, Folder 88)
    - Corporate sponsor envelopes, 2006-06 (Box 135, Folder 55)
    - Michelle Bachmann/MN Pride playing cards, 2006-07 (Box 133, Folder 82)
    - Gay Games join flyers, 2006-07 (Box 133, Folder 83)
    - Living Openly in Your Place of Worship, 2006-07 (Box 133, Folder 84)
    - Volunteer Leadership brochure, 2006-07 (Box 133, Folder 85)
    - Human Resources postcards, 2006-07 (Box 133, Folder 86)
    - Talk About It balloons, 2006-08 (Box 133, Folder 78)
    - Federal Club/Major Donor brochure, 2006-08 (Box 133, Folder 79)
    - State of the Workplace 2005/2006, 2006-08 (Box 133, Folder 80)
    - Human Resources welcome folders, 2006-08 (Box 133, Folder 81)
    - Faith and Fairness Minneapolis postcard, 2006-09 (Box 133, Folder 75)
    - Generation Equality stickers, 2006-09 (Box 133, Folder 76)
    - Corporate Equality Index 2006, 2006-09 (Box 133, Folder 77)
    - Out to Win wrappers, 2006-09 (Box 135, Folder 59)
    - Agenda business cards, 2006-10 (Box 133, Folder 74)
    - Congressional Scorecard 2006, 2006-10 (Box 134, Folder 29)
    - National Dinner program book, 2006-10 (Box 134, Folder 32)
    - Out to Vote stickers, 2006-10 (Box 134, Folder 33)
    - National Dinner photo coverage (Blade, Washington Post, Metro Weekly), 2006-10 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Buyers Guide, 2006-11 (Box 134, Folder 28)
    - Election Party Scorecard, 2006-11 (Box 134, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report 2006, 2006-12 (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - L Word raffle tickets, 2006-12 (Box 134, Folder 25)
    - Leading Equality, 2006-12 (Box 134, Folder 26)
    - Transgender Day of Remembrance photos - Blade, 2006-12 (Box 134, Folder 27)
    - Leading Equality, 2007 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - HBCU brochure, 2007-01 (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Equality from State to State, 2007-01 (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Heatherette hang tag, 2007-01 (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - All Children All Families, 2007-01 (Box 134, Folder 24)
    - Healthcare Equality Index postcards, 2007-02 (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - ENDA postcards, 2007-02 (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Corporate sponsor envelope, 2007-03 (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - Leadership Summit invitations, 2007-03 (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Love Conquers Hate (Hate Crimes postcards/board mtg), 2007-03 (Box 134, Folder 17)
    - Hate Crimes postcards to Senate, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 23)
    - National Dinner Save the Date cards, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 24)
    - Family Project brochure, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 25)
    - Coming Out as Transgender, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 26)
    - ENDA postcards, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 27)
    - Fight Hate Crime photo exhibit material, 2007-04 (Box 133, Folder 28)
    - HBCU DVD, 2007-04; DVD-2933 (Box 134, Folder 106)
    - Resources and Publications Pride Sheet, 2007-04 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Hate Crimes cards, 2007-05 (Box 133, Folder 22)
    - Corporate breakfast invitation, 2007-05 (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - True Colors Fight Hate Crimes stickers, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - State of the Workplace, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Hate Crimes True Colors cards, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - National Dinner Save the Date, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Leadership Institute invitation, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Small Business Basics, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 19)
    - Equality 08 stickers, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 20)
    - Hate Crimes Pride postcards, 2007-06 (Box 133, Folder 21)
    - Family Project All Children All Families brochure, 2007-07 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Understanding Transgender Issues: Donna's Rose's Story, 2007-07; DVD-2932 (Box 134, Folder 106)
    - Welcoming Schools postcards, 2007-08 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Leading Equality, 2007-09 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - HEI, 2007-09 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Workplace Out and Equal conference flyer, 2007-09 (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - National Dinner invitation, 2007-09 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Corporate Equality Series NY invite, 2007-09 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - 2007 National Dinner program book, 2007-10 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Annual report, 2007-10 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - National Dinner credentials, 2007-10 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - National Dinner auction books, 2007-10 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - National Dinner Preview Party brochure, 2007-10 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - All Children All Families revised brochure, 2007-10 (Box 134, Folder 69)
    - Buyers Guide 2008, 2007-11 (Box 134, Folder 65)
    - Equality Federal Club brochure revised, 2007-11 (Box 134, Folder 66)
    - Federal Club pledge card - smaller version, 2007-11 (Box 134, Folder 67)
    - 1640 Capital Campaign piece, 2007-11 (Box 134, Folder 68)
    - L Word raffle tickets, 2007-12 (Box 134, Folder 62)
    - Leadership Summit Save the Date, 2007-12 (Box 134, Folder 63)
    - Transgender Americans reprint, 2007-12 (Box 134, Folder 64)
    - Step Up to Leadership notebook, 2007-12 (Box 135, Folder 60)
    - State logo stickers, 2008-01 (Box 134, Folder 58)
    - Campaign manual, 2008-01 (Box 134, Folder 59)
    - Candidate manual envelopes, 2008-01 (Box 134, Folder 60)
    - Leading Equality, 2008-01 (Box 134, Folder 61)
    - Gen Eq postcards, 2008-02 (Box 133, Folder 57)
    - HRC folders, 2008-02 (Box 134, Folder 57)
    - Family Matters brochure, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 49)
    - Publications and Resources sheet, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 50)
    - Employment Opportunities AFP flyer, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 51)
    - Federal Club revised brochure, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 52)
    - GLBT Issues in the Workplace invitation, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 53)
    - Leadership Summit invites, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 54)
    - For the Bible Tells Me So field screening/raffle tickets, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 55)
    - True Colors tour flyer, 2008-03 (Box 134, Folder 56)
    - Federal Club folders, 2008-04 (Box 134, Folder 46)
    - Rock to Win DNC concert postcard, 2008-04 (Box 134, Folder 47)
    - At Home With invitation, 2008-04 (Box 134, Folder 48)
    - Rock to Win cards and Evolution of Talent, Winter 2007 (Box 134, Folder 35)
    - True Colors - HRC and PFLAG Pledge to Vote card, 2008-05 (Box 134, Folder 43)
    - Christian Sirano hangtag, 2008-05 (Box 134, Folder 44)
    - Healthcare Equality Index, 2008-05 (Box 134, Folder 45)
    - National Dinner Save the Date, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 37)
    - Leading Equality - Summer 08, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 38)
    - CA PAC contribution cards, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 39)
    - Vote Obama stickers, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 40)
    - CA Marriage Equality stickers, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 41)
    - Rock to Win revised cards, 2008-06 (Box 134, Folder 42)
    - OC Garden Party form, 2008-07 (Box 134, Folder 36)
    - All Children All Families 3rd edition palmcard, 2008-07 (Box 132, Folder 63)
    - Federal Club anniversary card, 2008-07 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - LGBT press credentials for DNC Diversity and Delegate lunch, 2008-08 (Box 133, Folder 72)
    - Transgender Inclusion in the Workplace, 2008-08 (Box 133, Folder 73)
    - National Dinner invitation, inserts and envelope, 2008-08 (Box 134, Folder 34)
    - Corporate Equality Index, 2008-09 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Step Up to Leadership letterhead, 2008-09 (Box 133, Folder 70)
    - Rock to Win Credentials, 2008-09 (Box 133, Folder 71)
    - Congressional Scorecard, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 63)
    - Leading Equality, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 64)
    - Annual Report 2008, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 65)
    - National Dinner Program book, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 66)
    - National Dinner tickets, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 68)
    - National Dinner auction book, 2008-10 (Box 133, Folder 69)
    - I'm Hype poster, 2008-10-03 (Box 133, Folder 67)
    - Buying for Equality, 2008-11 (Box 133, Folder 61)
    - Thanks for Giving capital campaign, 2008-11 (Box 133, Folder 62)
    - Federal Club newsletter, 2008-12 (Box 133, Folder 58)
    - Holiday cards, 2008-12 (Box 133, Folder 59)
    - Women's Holiday Party, 2008-12 (Box 133, Folder 60)
    - Leading Equality, 2009 (Box 133, Folder 52)
    - Leading Equality, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Utah Gala Save the Date, 2009-01 (Box 134, Folder 96)
    - Publications listing, 2009-02 (Box 133, Folder 56)
    - Leadership Summit invitations, 2009-03 (Box 133, Folder 54)
    - HRC Board bookmarks, 2009-03 (Box 133, Folder 55)
    - Transgender Visibility Guide, 2009-04 (Box 133, Folder 50)
    - Volunteer card, 2009-04 (Box 133, Folder 51)
    - National Dinner Save the Date business card, 2009-04 (Box 133, Folder 53)
    - Welcoming Schools CD and folder, 2009-04; DVD-2934 (Box 134, Folder 106)
    - General Membership brochure, 2009-05 (Box 133, Folder 49)
    - Federal Club pledge card, 2009-05 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Healthcare Equality Index, 2009-05 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Utah Speak the Truth program book, 2009-06 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Federal Club newsletter - Summer, 2009-06 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - National Dinner Save the Date, 2009-06 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Corporate Equality Index, 2009-09 (Box 133, Folder 48)
    - 2010 Corporate Equality Index, 2009-09 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - No Excuses folders, 2009-09 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - National Dinner invitation, 2009-09 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report fiscal year 2008, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 31)
    - National Dinner program book, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 101)
    - National Dinner table tents, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 102)
    - National Dinner silent auction book, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 103)
    - National Dinner tickets, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 104)
    - Degrees of Equality report, 2009-10 (Box 134, Folder 105)
    - National Dinner centerpieces, 2009-10 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Buyers Guide 2010, 2009-11 (Box 134, Folder 99)
    - Federal Club newsletter - Winter, 2009-11 (Box 134, Folder 100)
    - Holiday card, 2009-12 (Box 134, Folder 97)
    - DC Marriage Rally postcards, 2009-12 (Box 134, Folder 98)
    - Leading Equality, 2010 (Box 134, Folder 73)
    - Federal Club newsletter, 2010 (Box 134, Folder 78)
    - Equality from State to State, 2010-02 (Box 134, Folder 95)
    - Federal Club newsletter, 2010-03 (Box 134, Folder 83)
    - Join HRC brochure, 2010-03 (Box 134, Folder 88)
    - Publications one-sheet, 2010-03 (Box 134, Folder 89)
    - Repeal Don't Ask, Don't Tell cards, 2010-03 (Box 134, Folder 93)
    - Repeal Don't Ask, Don't Tell folders, 2010-03 (Box 134, Folder 94)
    - Tickets for Wedding Ceremonies in DC, 2010-03-09 (Box 134, Folder 91)
    - Wedding programs for DC marriages, 2010-03-09 (Box 134, Folder 92)
    - 2010-03-19 (Box 134, Folder 90)
    - Buyers Guide reprint, 2010-04 (Box 134, Folder 82)
    - National Dinner Save the Date card, 2010-04 (Box 134, Folder 84)
    - Buyers Guide reprint, 2010-04 (Box 134, Folder 85)
    - Federal Club newsletter - Spring, 2010-04 (Box 134, Folder 86)
    - Transgender Visibility Guide reprint, 2010-04 (Box 134, Folder 87)
    - Welcoming Schools CD, 2010-04; DVD-2935 (Box 134, Folder 106)
    - Equality Center Brochure, 2010-05 (Box 134, Folder 81)
    - National Dinner Save the Date, 2010-06 (Box 134, Folder 77)
    - HEI brochure, 2010-06 (Box 134, Folder 79)
    - Healthcare Equality Index, 2010-06 (Box 134, Folder 80)
    - Clergy Call postcards, 2010-07 (Box 134, Folder 76)
    - Straight Guide republish, 2010-09 (Box 134, Folder 74)
    - National Dinner invitations, 2010-09 (Box 134, Folder 75)
    - 2009/2010 Annual Report, 2010-10 (Box 134, Folder 71)
    - National Dinner program book, 2010-10 (Box 134, Folder 72)
    - Jeff Sheng DADT photo exhibit, 2010-11 (Box 134, Folder 70)
    - Board meeting buttons, 2012-03; MU-2506 (Box 133, Folder 101)
    - Americans for Marriage Equality button, 2012-03; MU-2507 (Box 133, Folder 102)
    - Equality State to State, 2012-04 (Box 133, Folder 44)
    - Youth Survey card, 2012-04 (Box 133, Folder 45)
    - Resource Guide to Coming Out, 2012-04 (Box 133, Folder 46)
    - Transgender Visibility Guide, 2012-04 (Box 133, Folder 47)
    - Revised Buyers Guides, 2012-05 (Box 133, Folder 42)
    - Federal Club newsletter - Spring, 2012-05 (Box 133, Folder 43)
    - Youth Report, 2012-06 (Box 133, Folder 41)
    - National Dinner Save the Date, 2012-07 (Box 133, Folder 40)
    - Federal Club newsletter - Summer, 2012-08 (Box 133, Folder 39)
    - National Dinner invitations, 2012-09 (Box 133, Folder 37)
    - Coming Out as a Straight Supporter, 2012-09-28 (Box 133, Folder 38)
    - National Dinner tickets and hotel key, 2012-10 (Box 133, Folder 35)
    - National Dinner Program book, 2012-10 (Box 133, Folder 36)
    - Municipal Equality Index, 2012-11 (Box 133, Folder 34)
    - Annual Report 2012, 2012-12 (Box 133, Folder 32)
    - Holiday card, 2012-12 (Box 133, Folder 33)
    - Congressional Scorecard - 112th Congress, 2013-01 (Box 133, Folder 30)
    - Buyers Guide, 2013-01 (Box 133, Folder 31)
    - Corporate Equality Index 2013, 2013-12 (Box 133, Folder 29)
  - Equality Magazine
    - Winter 2003, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 53)
    - Summer 2004, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 52)
    - Fall 2005, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 49)
    - Summer 2005, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 50)
    - Spring 2005, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 51)
    - Winter 2006/07, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 45)
    - Summer 2006, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 47)
    - Winter 2006, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 48)
    - Fall 2006, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 54)
    - Fall 2007, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 41)
    - Summer 2007, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 42)
    - Spring 2007, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 43)
    - Buyers Guide Bind-in, 2007-01 (Box 135, Folder 46)
    - Bind in for Equality Mag, 2007-03 (Box 135, Folder 44)
    - Summer 2008, 2008 (Box 135, Folder 38)
    - Winter 2008, 2008 (Box 135, Folder 40)
    - Spring 2008, 2008-05 (Box 135, Folder 39)
    - Spring 2009, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 36)
    - Winter 2009, 2009 (Box 135, Folder 37)
    - Summer 2009, 2009-06 (Box 135, Folder 35)
    - Fall 2009, 2009-09 (Box 135, Folder 34)
    - Fall 2010, 2010 (Box 135, Folder 30)
    - Summer 2010, 2010 (Box 135, Folder 31)
    - Spring 2010, 2010 (Box 135, Folder 32)
    - Winter 2010, 2010 (Box 135, Folder 33)
    - Spring 2011, 2011 (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Winter 2011, 2011 (Box 135, Folder 29)
    - Winter 2012, 2011-03 (Box 135, Folder 25)
    - Summer 2011, 2011-07 (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - Fall 2011, 2011-11 (Box 135, Folder 26)
    - Spring 2012, 2012-06 (Box 135, Folder 24)
    - Summer 2012, 2012-09 (Box 135, Folder 23)
    - Fall 2012, 2012-12 (Box 135, Folder 22)
    - Fall 2013, 2013 (Box 135, Folder 19)
    - Winter 2013, 2013-03 (Box 135, Folder 21)
    - Spring 2013, 2013-06 (Box 135, Folder 20)
    - Late Fall, 2013-12 (Box 135, Folder 18)
    - Late Winter, 2014-03 (Box 135, Folder 17)
    - Spring 2014, 2014-05 (Box 135, Folder 16)
    - Late Summer/Early Fall, 2014-09 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Winter 2014, 2014-12 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Late Winter/Early Spring, 2015-03 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Late Spring/Early Summer, 2015-07 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Summer 2015, 2015-09 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Fall 2015, 2015-11 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Advertising
    - Buying for Equality print ads/ various GLBT publications, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 62)
    - Buying for Equality print ads/ various GLBT publications, 2006 (Box 136, Folder 5-6)
    - Talk About It ad - University of Michigan, 2006-10 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Equality/CEI ad - Gay City News, 2006-10-12 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Employment ad - Metro Weekly, 2006-10-12 (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Employment ad - Washington Blade, 2006-10-13 (Box 132, Folder 14)
    - Equality CEI ad - New York Blade, 2006-10-16 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    - Equality CEI ad - Dallas Voice, 2006-10-20 (Box 132, Folder 12)
    - Equality CEI ad - New York Blade, 2006-10-23 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    - Buying for Equality - Gay Press ads, Summer (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Tyron Garner Tribute ad - Out Smart, 2006-11 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Out in Scripture ad - Christian Century, 2006-11 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Equality/Wall St ad and story, 2006-11 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Buyer's Guide ad, 2006-11 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Curve Buyer's Guide ad, 2006-11 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - New York Times Equality ad, 2006-12 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Holiday Party ad - Metro Weekly/Washington Blade, 2006-12 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Buying for Equality - Frontiers and OutFront Colorado, 2006-12 (Box 135, Folder 61)
    - Dallas Black Tie Thank You ad, 2007-01 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Advocate Out Vision Ad, 2007-01 (Box 132, Folder 28)
    - Agenda ad campaign, 2007-01 (Box 132, Folder 29)
    - Out Magazine - 2007 Vision ad, 2007-02 (Box 132, Folder 27)
    - True Colors ads - DC, 2007-03 (Box 132, Folder 25)
    - Matthew Shepard Foundation Program Book ad, 2007-03 (Box 132, Folder 26)
    - Roll Call Hate Crimes ad, 2007-05-03 (Box 132, Folder 24)
    - Pride Magazine, 2007-06 (Box 132, Folder 23)
    - HRC Save the Date Dinner ad, 2007-07-08 (Box 132, Folder 22)
    - Faith Leaders Against Hate Roll Call, 2007-07-10 (Box 132, Folder 21)
    - DC Store Moving Sale ads, 2007-07-12 (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - The Truth About Hate Crime Legislation - USA Today, 2007-07-16 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - National Dinner Pelosi ad - MW/Blade, 2007-07-19 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Buying for Equality gift guide, 2007-12 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Modern Luxury/HRC Dinner - Charity Datebook ad, 2008-03 (Box 132, Folder 56)
    - National Dinner Kick Off ad - Washington Blade, 2008-03-07 (Box 132, Folder 54)
    - Dallas Thank You ad - Dallas Voice, 2008-03-21 (Box 132, Folder 55)
    - Youth Pride photo and ad - Metro Weekly, 2008-04 (Box 132, Folder 53)
    - Washington Mystics - Metro Weekly, 2008-05-29 (Box 132, Folder 52)
    - Rock to Win - Metromode, 2008-06-2008-07 (Box 132, Folder 47)
    - Rock to Win - OutFront, Co., 2008-06 (Box 132, Folder 49)
    - Store ad - Metro Weekly/Pride Guide, 2008-06-10 (Box 132, Folder 50)
    - Christian Siriano ad - Metro Weekly, 2008-06-12 (Box 132, Folder 51)
    - Lambada program book, 2008-06-21 (Box 132, Folder 48)
    - Rock to Win - Boulder, Weekly/Metromode, 2008-07-17 (Box 132, Folder 45)
    - Rock to Win ads - OutFront/Boulder Weekly, 2008-07-23 (Box 132, Folder 46)
    - Rock to Win - DNC book, 2008-08 (Box 132, Folder 44)
    - Rock to Win - OutFront, Co., 2008-08-20 (Box 132, Folder 43)
    - National Dinner - Metro Weekly, 2008-09-11 (Box 132, Folder 42)
    - National Dinner Raffle ad, 2008-09-19 (Box 132, Folder 41)
    - Faith and Fairness - 4 ads - Brainard Dispatch MN, 2008-10 (Box 132, Folder 33)
    - Metro Weekly store ads, 2008-10 (Box 132, Folder 34)
    - HRC/National Trust for Historic Preservation ad, 2008-10 (Box 132, Folder 36)
    - Vote Pro-bono ad, 2008-10 (Box 132, Folder 37)
    - Metro Weekly Dinner ad, 2008-10-02 (Box 132, Folder 40)
    - Washington Blade Raffle and Dinner ad, 2008-10-03 (Box 132, Folder 39)
    - National Dinner Thank You ad and photos from Blade and MW, 2008-10-10 (Box 132, Folder 32)
    - Election night ads - Metro Weekly/Washington Blade, 2008-10-23-2008-10-24 (Box 132, Folder 38)
    - Election night ads - Metro Weekly/Washington Blade, 2008-10-30-2008-10-31 (Box 132, Folder 35)
    - HRC U student ads, 2008-11 (Box 132, Folder 31)
    - Buyers Guide ads, 2008-11-2008-12 (Box 132, Folder 92)
    - Metro Weekly store ads, 2008-11 (Box 132, Folder 93)
    - Family Project adoption campaign - Frontiers, 2008-11 (Box 132, Folder 94)
    - Adoption ads (Metro Weekly/Washington Blade), 2008-11-27-2008-12-05 (Box 132, Folder 30)
    - Metro Weekly store ads, 2008-12 (Box 132, Folder 90)
    - Buyers Guide ad campaign, 2008-12 (Box 132, Folder 91)
    - Out for Equality - MW and Washington Blade, 2008-12-12 (Box 132, Folder 86)
    - Dallas Black Tie ad - Dallas Voice, 2008-12-19 (Box 132, Folder 89)
    - Men's Holiday Party ad - MW, 2008-12-31 (Box 132, Folder 88)
    - Inauguration Activities ad - Washington Blade, 2009-01-16 (Box 132, Folder 87)
    - Dallas Voice - Best Political Organization Thank You ad, 2009-03 (Box 132, Folder 85)
    - Capital Pride Heroes ad, 2009-06 (Box 132, Folder 83)
    - HRC Pride store ad, 2009-06 (Box 132, Folder 84)
    - Capital Pride Heroes ad - Washington Blade, 2009-06-12 (Box 132, Folder 81)
    - National Dinner Table Captain ad - Washington Blade, 2009-06-12 (Box 132, Folder 82)
    - National Dinner ad - DC Modern Luxury, 2009-08 (Box 132, Folder 79)
    - National Dinner Table Captain ad - Washington Blade, 2009-08-14 (Box 132, Folder 80)
    - Lexus National Dinner Raffle ad - DC Modern Luxury, 2009-09 (Box 132, Folder 77)
    - National Dinner ads - Metro Weekly - Washington Blade, 2009-09-17-2009-09-18 (Box 132, Folder 78)
    - DC Modern Luxury National Dinner Thank You/Sponsor ad, 2009-10 (Box 132, Folder 72)
    - Legalize Gay/American Apparel t-shirt ad - Metro Weekly, 2009-10-08 (Box 132, Folder 74)
    - National Dinner Thank You Sponsor ad - Washington Blade and Metro Weekly, 2009-10-08-2009-10-09 (Box 132, Folder 75)
    - National Equality March ad - Washington Blade and Metro Weekly, 2009-10-08-2009-10-09 (Box 132, Folder 76)
    - Washington Blade 40th Anniversary ad, 2009-10-16 (Box 132, Folder 73)
    - Blade/DC Agenda full page ad, 2009-11-20 (Box 132, Folder 71)